Guide to the Medical Center records, 1825-2005 RG0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Medical Center records
1825-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Hospital
George Washington University. Medical Center
RG0007
131.5 Linear Feet
Collection includes personnel files, minutes, correspondence, yearbooks, newsletters, publications, photographs, scrapbooks, telephone directories, films, and videotapes.
Restrictions on Access
Series 1, 2, 3, 11, 12, and 13 are closed to research for 75 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Materials transfered to University Archives by the Medical Center.
Historical Note
The George Washington University Medical Center is comprised of School of Medicine and Health Sciences, the University Hospital (including the Women's Board, which was formed in 1898), and the University Clinic (Ambulatory Care Center).
The medical school was opened in 1825 and is the eleventh oldest in the nation. From 1868-1973 it was located at 1335 H Street, NW. In 1973 it moved to Walter G. Ross Hall and the Himmelfarb Medical Library. All aspects of the Medical Center -hospital, medical school, and research facilities - were centralized at last. The hospital had been located at 1335 H Street until 1948, when a new hospital was built on Washington Circle.
A new hospital was constructed in 2002 across the street from the old one. The University Clinic opened in 1969 on Pennsylvania Avenue and was expanded to house the Ambulatory Care Center in 1988.
In 1981 the Medical Center's staff made front-page news when President Reagan, shot at close range, was rushed to the GW emergency room. The fine service that saved the president's life was commemorated 10 years later by the establishment of the Ronald Reagan Institute of Emergency Medicine to train emergency system coordinators and pursue basic and clinical research in emergency medicine.
The Medical Center publishes Progress (1989-Present), which evolved from the Friday Report (1970-89), and GW Health and Medicine magazine (1965-Present). The Vice President for Health Affairs (which oversees the Medical Center) reports to the President.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include personnel files, minutes, correspondence, yearbooks, newsletters, publications, photographs, negatives, by-laws, scrapbooks, telephone directories, films, and videotapes. They range in date from dates from 1825-2011, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Director of the Medical Center. Note that not all series have been processed. Please see staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into thirty-one series: Personnel files; Medical staff office files; Personnel files; Articles and studies; Reprints; Chartering ceremony (currently missing); Photographs and negatives; Reports; Statistics of medical school; Women's board; Committee files; Inactive physicians files; Inactive physicians files; Women's board; Alumni Association for Health Services Management; Health Services Management and Policy Alumni Association; Women's board; Telephone directories; Publication; Department of Pharmacology reprints; Films; School of Public Health and Health Services; Women's Board; Photographs, papers, and videotapes; Yearbooks; Friday Report; GW Medicine/Health magazine; Photographs; State Health Notes newsletter; Progress newsletter; Records.
Collection note
There is no series number 31.
Scrapbooks; Physicians; Washington (D.C.); Faculty; Students; Budget; Publications; By-laws; Employees; Staff; Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Nursing; Medical care; Photographs; George Washington University. Hospital; George Washington University--Alumni and alumnae; George Washington University. School of Medicine and Health Sciences; George Washington University
- Personnel files, circa 1970-circa 1989; RG0007 Series 1; 34.5 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of personnel files of inactive medical and dental staff over age 65. The dates of the materials is not readily attainable, but generally fall in the range of the 1970's-80's.
  - Lande, Ian M., undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Department: Diag. Rad
  - Lando, Howard, M., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Department: Med
  - Lane, Jeffrey H., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Department: Ob-Gyn
  - Lang, Louis R., undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lang, John A., undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Department:Med
  - Lanier, Keith, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lanter, David L., undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lao, Anita I., undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lapin, Alfred R., undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Last, Sandra P., undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Department:Rad
  - LLatchis, Erika, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Department:Ob-Gyn un/pt
  - Latchis, Kenneth S., undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Latham, Wilbur D., undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Department:Plastic Surg.
  - Latkin, Peter C., undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Department:Allergy
  - Latven, Kasty C., undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lavine, Robert L., undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lavine, Stanford A., undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Department:Ortho un/pt
  - Lawrence, William H., undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Department:Neuro
  - Lawrenz, David R., undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Department:Neurological surg.
  - Lawson, Thomas L, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Department:Asst. Prof/Rad
  - Lazarus, Allan M., undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Department:Ob/Gyn
  - Leadbetter, Wayne B., undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Department:Ortho
  - Lebensohn, Zigmond M., undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Department:Psych Ctsy
  - Leber, Paul D., undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Department:Psych
  - Lederman, Martin E., undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Department:Opthal
  - Lee, Rory T., undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Lee, Sang N., undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Department:Asst. Prof/rad
  - Lee, Sontaek T., undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Lefkowitz, Leonard, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Department:Ped
  - Leibenhaut, Susan, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Lesar, May S, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Lessin, Bruce E., undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Lester, Arthur H., undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Levin, Bradley H., undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Department:Surg
  - Levin, Eleanor, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Levister, Ernest C., undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Levitsky, Leon R., undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Levy, Arnold G., undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Department:Med/cliniccalinst
  - Levy, Charles S., undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Levy, Marie-Louise, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Department:Anest
  - Lewicki, Ann M., undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Lewis, Bradley E., undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Lewis, David M., undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Lewis, James H., undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Lieberman, Norman A., undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Lien, Jean M., undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Lilly, John Russell, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Lindeman, Robert J., undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Lindenoth, Norman W., undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Department:Health Care sci
  - Lindsay Jr., Joseph, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Lines, Lawrence G., undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Lipsit, Edward R., undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Lisa,George, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Department:OphTh.
  - Litman, Deborah, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Department:Med-Rhematology
  - Liu, Ghia C., undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Loeffler, Robert G., undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Loewenstein, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Lofft, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Love, Patricia, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Lowe, John A., undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Ludwig, Carol L., undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Lukasik, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Lussky, Donald, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Lux, Warren E., undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - McCartee, Carl C., undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Department:Ortho sx
  - Macoviak John, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
    Department:Sug Tps
  - Magassy, Csaba L., undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
    Department:Surg.
  - Mahdavi, Iradj, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Majd, Massoud, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
    Department:Rad/Child Health
  - Major, Mary J., undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Malone, Daniel R., undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Department:Emer. Med
  - Malone, Michael J., undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Man, Philip S., undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Manguikian, Dertad, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Marak, George, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Marban, Lee, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Marc, Joseph A., undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Marcellus, Harvey, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
    Department:Physicians asst
  - March, Lewis E., undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Marchese, Eugenia Z., undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Mardelli, Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Mardiat, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Margulies, David M., undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Marinelli, Kathleen A., undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
    Department:N.B. Services
  - Markoff, Lewis J., undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Marks, Irving L., undated (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Marsh, Henry B., undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Marshall, Lewis W., undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Martin, Lisa M., undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
    Department:Int. Med/Card
  - Marting, Theordor, undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Martino, Alberto, undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Marx, Terry M., undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
    Department:Neoat/HCS
  - Matini, Khosrow, undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
    Department: Hand Surg
  - May, Dean F, undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - McCullars, George M., undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
    Department: Cipath
  - McElroy Jr, Ross A., undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
    Department:Psych un-pt
  - McKay, Douglas W., undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
    Department:Professor/Orth surg
  - McKelway, William P., undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - McKittrick, Alice M., undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Department:
  - McSweeney, William J., undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Department:Dad/Child health
  - Meek, Donald C., undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Department:Ob
  - Meisler, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Rad
  - Merlino, Robin Med, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mermel, John F., undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Department:Med Un/pt
  - Messore, Alfred M., undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Department:Psych un/pt
  - Meyers, Andrew V., undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Department:Child healthand dev.
  - Mickel, Huberts, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Midgley, Frank M., undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Department:e Surg/Card Thorac
  - Mier, Richard J., undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Department:Ped/Clinical inst
  - Milhorat, Thomas., undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Miller, Bess I., undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Department:Health Care sci/med.
  - Miller, George F., undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Miller, Frederick N., undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Department: B. Services
  - Miller, Marilea K., undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Department:Neoat
  - MilIon, Dorothy E., undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Department: Med. Un-p
  - Mills, Earl C., undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Department:Neurosung
  - Milmoe, Gregory, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Department:Ped Ent/Neoat
  - Mira-Hernandez, Jose L., undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Department:Pathology
  - Mirkin, Gabriel B., undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Department:Ped.
  - Mirmirani, Nooreddin, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Mitchell, Arthur V., undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Mitchell, Donald E., undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Department:Dermat
  - Mitchell, Hersert N., undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mitchell, Joyce M., undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Department: Emer. Med
  - Modiin, Albert J., undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Mohamadi, Mahmood, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Department:Endocrinology
  - Molchon, Andrew B., undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Department:Psych and behave, sci
  - Mondino, Marta M., undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Department:Anest.
  - Moniz, Albert, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Moore, John W., undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Moore, Pamela R., undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Moore, W., undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Department:Tabb Med.
  - Mopsik, Edward, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Department:Oral. Surg
  - Moretti, John F., undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Morowitz, David A., undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Department:Gastro
  - Morrissey, William F., undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Roberts, Morton J., undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Department:Clinical inst/ob-gyn
  - Mosher, Don T., undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Moyer, Paul R., undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Moyle, William D., undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Mukhopadhyay, Madan G., undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Muller, Alfred E., undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Murphy, Michael A., undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Department:Ob-Gyn
  - Murphy, Thomas N., undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    Department:Chd/Pulmonary
  - Murray, Anne L., undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Mussenden, Caryl, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Nachajaski, Peter J., undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Nagelberg, Steven B., undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Narang, Anil K., undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Nason, Stephen S., undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Nasou, John P., undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Nassif, Thomas J., undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Natelson, Benjamin H., undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Naughton, John P., undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
    Department:Rehab. Med
  - Naulty, Cheryl, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
    Department:Child Health and dev
  - Nelson, Bertel, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
    Department:Med.
  - Nelson, Fred R., undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
    Department:Ortho. Surg
  - Neville Jr., Rufus L., undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
    Department: Surg/urolo
  - Neviaser, Thomas J., undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Newton, Howard J., undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Neblett, Keith H., undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Nielsen, Arthur C., undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Niles Jr, John H., undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Nsien, Ephraim Int., undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
    Department:Med. Gastro
  - 0' Connor, John J., undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
    Department:Surg, Colo-Rectal/Asst. Prof.
  - O'donghue, J., undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
    Department:MorganMed/Infec. Diseases
  - O'Dowd, Gerard J., undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - O'Leary, Dennis S., undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Department:Med and Hematology
  - O'Leary, Margaret R., undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - O'Weiss, Zacharia M., undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Obele, Emmanuel O., undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Okehi, Chukeumeka, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Oler, Wesley M., undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Oliver Jr, Cap H., undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
    Department:Med Un-fl
  - Oliver, Gregory C., undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Olness, Karen N., undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Department:Ped Pt. Med
  - Olson, Hard in E., undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Olson, Jeffrey J., undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
    Department:Neuro. Surg
  - O'Neill, John F., undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
    Department:Ophthal
  - Oranburg, Phil lip R., undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
    Department:Med/Card
  - Oredein, Olugbenga S., undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Otchin, Neil S., undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Ottenberg, Gilbert, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Ottenritter, Lewis A., undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
    Department:Otho
  - Ozer, Mark N., undated (Box 2, Folder 88)
    Department:child Health and dev
  - Sheagren, John N., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Shelburne, Samuel A., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Department:Neurol
  - Sherer, Peter B., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sherrv, Mohamad N., undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Shinder, Sharadchandra G., undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sidou, VickieAnest, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Silber, Thomas J., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sim, Diane C., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Simeone, Richard J., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Simon, Ernest R., undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - SimoPoulos, Artemis P., undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Simpson, Robert L., undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Simrel, Kermit O., undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sinderson, Thomas G., undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Department:Card/Med
  - Singer, Alan H., undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Department:Oral Surg
  - Singer, Herbert C., undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Department:Asst.Clinical Prof/Med
  - Skilling, John C., undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Sklarew, Bruce H., undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Skyler, Jay S., undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Slovin, Alvin J., undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Deborah, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Donald R., undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Smith, Jean A., undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Department:Health Care Sci/Me
  - Smith, Norman J., undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Smith, Ronald W., undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Smits, Helen I., undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Department:Med/Health Care Sci
  - Snow, Jerry A., undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Department:Med-Cardiovas
  - Snyder, Joseph, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Soifer, Edgar H., undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Solack, George A., undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Soliman, NaderAnest, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Solomon, Steven I., undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Soverow, Gary J., undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Speller, Jeffrey L., undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Spence, Ian J., undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Department:Urology
  - Sprague, David S., undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Srabstein, Jorge C., undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Stallings Jr., James H., undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Stanton, Larry W., undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Starr, Dorothy, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Stazio, Antonio, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
    Department:Neurolgy
  - Steinberg, David L., undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Steinglass, Peter J., undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Department:Psych and Behav.Serv
  - Stephen, James M., undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
    Department:Emer.Med
  - Sterling, William N., undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Stern, George A., undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Stern, Melvin J., undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Stevens, Jeol, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Stiegler Jr., Charles F., undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Stiller, John W., undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
    Department:Neurology
  - Stockton, William J., undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Stohlman, John W., undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Stokes, Chauncey, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Stow, M.Noel, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Storm, Randle H., undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
    Department:Int.Med/Card
  - Straus, Donald, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
    Department:Peds/Ctsy
  - Stroud, Robert M., undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Stubbs, Peggy A., undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Stuckey, John H., undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
    Int.Med
  - Sullivan, Thomas J., undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Sutherland III, Earl W., undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Swanberg, Louise E., undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Swann Jr., Louis W., undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Tabb, Marvin N., undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Tanenbaum, Herbert L., undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
    Department:Card
  - Tape, Hazel M., undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
    Department:Health care sci
  - Taylor, Jack B., undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Tene, CharlesD., undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
    Department:D.S.Oral Surg
  - Terlinsky, Alan, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
    Department:Med (Renal)
  - Terrell Jr., William, undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Teychenne, Paul F., undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
    Department:Neurology/Asst.Department:Prof
  - Thaler, Frank H., undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Thomas, Michael N., undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
    B.Services
  - Thomas, Patricia A., undated (Box 5, Folder 74)
    Department:Health Care Sci/Med
  - Thompson, Lewis W., undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
    Department:Plastic Surg FL
  - Thompson, Thomas C., undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Thompson, William F., undated (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Ticktin, Howard E., undated (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Tidey, George F., undated (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Tievsky, Andrew L., undated (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Timins, Julie, undated (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Tinker, Bruce P., undated (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Todaro, Jane L., undated (Box 5, Folder 83)
    Department:Ped Un/pt
  - Tolson Jr., Robert E., undated (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Tompkins, William G., undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Toomey, Kathleen E., undated (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Trachman, Susan B., undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Tralka, George A., undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Trenis, John W., undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Tsakonas, John W., undated (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Tsakonas, John S., undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Tung, Tran M., undated (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Tuori, Sasan L., undated (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Turbiak, Thomas W., undated (Box 5, Folder 94)
    Department:Emer Med
  - Turner, Raymond W., undated (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Turner, Robert T., undated (Box 5, Folder 96)
    Department:Int.Med
  - Turner, William L., undated (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Turner-Warwick, Richard T., undated (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Continuation of Hearing on the privileges of Dr. Atin Guha and Dr. Jay Ocuin, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Investigation: Patrick Coyne, M.D., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Investigation: Ralph DePalma, M.D., 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hearing on the privileges of Dr. Atin Guha and Dr. Jay Ocuin, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - MacDonald, Gerard Fintan, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Maciulla, Louis, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Maclean, Marion, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - MacMillian. Albert Slocomb, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Maganzini, Herman, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Maret, Raymond, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Martel, Leon, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Martin, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Martin, George, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Martin, Dean, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Masterson, James, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - May, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - McCall, Marvin, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - McCarrick, James P., undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - McCarthy, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - McCarthy, Mor James, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - McCawley, Walter, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - McCormack, Charles, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - McCune, Wallace, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - McCurdy, Harry, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - McDermott, Harry, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - McDonald, James F., undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - McEne r ney, Charle s, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Mclntire, Ross, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - McKay, James, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - McLain, George, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Mendelsohn, Matthew, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Merchant, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Metcalf, George, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Miller, William W., Jr., undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Miller, Robert, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Mitchell, Reginald, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Morrison, Samuel, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Moskow, Samuel, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Mousel, Lyoyd, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Murphy, John C., undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - MacDonald, Gordon R., undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - MacKenzie, Thayer, undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - MacMurray, Frank, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - MacPherson, Archibald, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Madden, Leland S., undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Madigan, Eromett Patrick, undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Madigan, Howard Stone, undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Magal, Ivan V., undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Maganias, Nicholas, undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Magnant, George, undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Maier, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Maksim, Goerge, undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Mandes, James, undated (Box 11, Folder 49)